[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Cast Away, what type of clothing does Chuck find in one of the packages?", "correct_answer": "Party dress", "incorrect_answers": ["Tuxedo", "Kimono", "Bathing suit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the tagline for the 1994 action comedy movie True Lies, directed by James Cameron?", "correct_answer": "When he said I do, he never said what he did.", "incorrect_answers": ["He lied about lying, and then he lied again.", "He was so good at lying that he got confused.", "Dont simply hide the truth. Lie about it!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It has been proved that drinking only bottled water can have this effect on your health.", "correct_answer": "Increase in dental problems", "incorrect_answers": ["Increase in body fat", "Increase in weight", "Increase in heart disease"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The original name of the Beatles song, Eleanor Rigby, was Miss Daisy Hawkins.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Cerato essence is suitable for horses that withhold their emotions despite suffering from a pain or disease.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these characters created by French writer Alexandre Dumas is not correctly matched with the novel?", "correct_answer": "G\u00e9rard de Villefort - Twenty Years After", "incorrect_answers": ["Milady de Winter - The Three Musketeers", "DArtagnan - Twenty Years After", "La Mole - Queen Margot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When anxious, the koala produces a loud sound similar to the cry made by this creature.", "correct_answer": "Human baby", "incorrect_answers": ["Baby bear", "Crow", "Rabbit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average maximal speed a lion can reach?", "correct_answer": "35 mph / 56 km/h", "incorrect_answers": ["45 mph / 72 km/h", "20 mph / 32 km/h", "40 mph / 64 km/h"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Patrick Dempsey plays the role of the Mayor of New York in the movie Sweet Home Alabama.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of character does Whoopi Goldberg play in the 1999 drama movie Girl, Interrupted?", "correct_answer": "Nurse", "incorrect_answers": ["A writer", "A woman with a mental disorder", "A cook"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The average woman will wear different bra sizes in her life, due to gravity, pregnancy and weight changes. How many times will she change her size?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "3", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Raccoons are omnivorous animals but they have a preference for this type of food.", "correct_answer": "Fruits and nuts", "incorrect_answers": ["Invertebrates", "Birds", "Fish"]}]